inbox-labs.com 2015-10-13

# InboxLabs - Outstanging Email Marketing

The Privacy Policy covers InboxLabs' (“the Company”) treatment of personally identifiable information that is collected when the subscribers agree to receive e-mail ad messages from the Company or one of the Company's advertisers. This type of agreement on behalf of a subscriber constitutes a permission-based opt-in. The Company operates exclusively in permission based advertising and is compliant with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003. 

### Subscription process

In order for a subscriber to be considered opted-in he or she must agree to provide their email address plus mandatory personal information to InboxLabs, including gender, first name, last name, address and phone number. The subscribers can volunteer additional personal demographic information, such as age, income, occupation and more. 

After the initial opt-in, each subscriber receives an automatic confirmation email. 

### Unsubscription process

A subscriber may unsubscribe at any time. Each email communication sent from the Company contains at least 2 opt-out vehicles, identified as hyperlinks or physical addresses of the advertisers or list owner. Also, the Company's advertising partner may insert an opt-out hyperlink. The opt-out is quick, easy, and also in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003. Opt-outs are processed no later than 72 hours after submitted. 

### Data sources

The Privacy Policy applies to subscribers that agreed to receive e-mail marketing from the Company, whether at the Company's website, e-mail, third party partner websites or otherwise.

The Company may share the subscriber’s personal information and the Company may work with other businesses (providers of direct-marketing services and applications, including lookup and reference, data enhancement, suppression and validation) to bring selected retail offers to the subscribers.

The Company purchases and manages lists generated by trustworthy partners who follow the same guidelines on privacy.

The Company reserves the right to provide, aggregate or group data about the Company's subscribers for lawful purposes. Aggregate or group data is data that describes the demographics, usage, or characteristics of the Company's participants as a group, not disclosing personally identifiable information. By opening a Company account, the subscriber agrees to allow the Company to provide such aggregate data to 3rd parties. Additionally, the Company may employ clear gifs to track the pages that our subscribers visit at the Company's website for purposes of targeting future campaigns.

The Company also reserves the right to release subscriber information in the event that the Company believes that the subscriber is using, or has used, Services of the Company in violation of the terms and conditions, to commit unlawful acts, if the information is subpoenaed, if the Company is sold or acquired, or when the Company deems it necessary or appropriate. By agreeing to these terms, the subscriber hereby consents to the disclosure of any record or communication to any 3rd party when the Company, in its sole discretion, determines the disclosure to be appropriate. The Company does not collect credit card numbers, bank information or social security numbers.

The Company does not market gambling, religious , politic or pornographic offers of any kind.

We endeavor to safeguard and protect our subscriber information. When subscriber submit information at the website, their information is protected. The privacy of the consumer's personal information is essential to us. The Company's employees are committed to the Company's privacy and security policies. The servers that the Company stores personally-identifiable information in are kept in a secure physical environment.

Users under 18 years of age are not allowed to participate in sweepstakes or game promotion offered by the Company. No information should be submitted to, or posted at, any the Company's websites by visitors under 18 years of age without the prior consent of their parent or guardian. Notwithstanding the foregoing, children 13 years of age and younger are not permitted to access the Company's website and the Company does not knowingly collect personal information from such children. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children.

The Company does not endorse, nor is responsible for the accuracy of, the privacy policies and/or terms and conditions of each of the advertisers and/or 3rd parties accessible through the Company's website.

By using this site, including, without limitation, signing up for offers and/or continuing to receive information from the Company, consumers agree to the Company Privacy Policy. The Company reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, and/or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Company's website. Please check this page periodically for changes. The subscriber’s continued use of the Company's website or acceptance of our emails following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept these changes and agree to continue receiving emails from us. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please send an email to [contact@inbox-labs.com](mailto:contact@inbox-labs.com) .

### Unsubscription

A subscriber may unsubscribe at any time. To do so, simply click the remove link in the first sentence of any of the Company's offers. You may also remove yourself from our database at any time by emailing us at [optout@inbox-labs.com](mailto:optout@inbox-labs.com). Please type "OPT-OUT" in subject line. 

Unsubscribe from our List Alerts >> [optout@inbox-labs.com](mailto:optout@inbox-labs.com)

Unsubscribe from our Corporate communications >> [optout@inbox-labs.com](mailto:optout@inbox-labs.com)
